Run, Omoi
What?!
Did you say Omoi deserted
the battlefield?!
帰って来い　友よ！　戦友よ！
Is this true, Kakashi?
ええい！　オモイのヤツめ
何を考えておる！？
Yes. Reports say he ran from
his post after saying
he needed to leave for a bit.
一人でも戦力が減れば→
即　隊の壊滅に
繋がりかねないという→
Omoi! Why?
Why would he do that?
この状況がわからんのか！？
Come back…
my comrade-in-arms!
《カルイ：雷影様　アホか！
Damn it, Omoi!
逃げたこと信じてるのかよ！？》
カ…　カルイ！
What was he thinking?!
Doesn't he know the circumstances
that we're in?
ヤツは　ああ見えるけど
そんなヤワな男じゃないよ。
That even losing one man could
decrease the military strength of the unit!
Lord Raikage!
わ…　わしだって　そう思いたい。
That's crazy! Who'd believe that crap
about him deserting!
じゃが　敵前逃亡は→
K-Karui…
雲隠れの里では
重罪にあたいする。
He may look it,
but he's not a coward!
He'd never run away
in the face of the enemy.
（サイ）思い当たることが
一つあります。
It's got to be some mistake!
Well… I don't want to believe it either.
But deserting one's post
under enemy fire is
considered a serious offense
in the Hidden Cloud Village. So…
One thing comes to mind.
Is that you, Sai?
Just before Omoi left,
we received a report that
白ゼツの大群に包囲されて
動きがとれないとのことでした。
the unit on Battlefield Seven
was under attack
and needed reinforcements.
その数　２，０００体と。
When he heard that,
I believe I saw Omoi go pale.
近くにまわせる人員はなく→
もちこたえるよう
返答しています。
We received a distress call
asking for reinforcements
four hours ago.
それ以後は　何も…。
They were surrounded by
おそらく　オモイさんは
そこへ向かったんじゃないかと。
a large number of White Zetsu
and couldn't move.
Two thousand of them.
Two thousand…
We had no troops nearby,
so we told them to hang tight.
We haven't heard from them since.
Perhaps that's where
Omoi was headed…
Who's holding down
Battlefield Seven?
（綱手）第７戦線は　どこの部隊が？
The Amphibious Search and Destroy Unit.
水陸遊撃部隊です。
Most of them are from
Hidden Mist Village
主に霧隠れの里による部隊で→
and 24 of them
were deployed to the front.
２４名が配置されております。
Hidden Mist… Why would Omoi go?
霧隠れ…。　なぜ　オモイが？
We received a disturbing message
right after that.
直後に気になる報告が。
A supply unit which was on the road
near Battlefield Seven
第７戦線に近い地点を
移動中の補給部隊が→
never reached their destination.
目標地点に　いまだ
到達してないとのことです。
Maybe they went to aid
the Amphibious S&D Unit?
もしや　水陸遊撃隊の
応援に向かったのでは？
This supply unit…
Who are they?
補給部隊は　どこの？
The Hidden Cloud's…
Thundercloud Unit!
雲隠れの…　雷雲隊。
What did you say?
何だと？
雷雲隊！
The Thundercloud Unit…
What kind of unit is it?
雷雲隊とは　どんな部隊だ？
It's made up of seven,
twelve to thirteen-year-olds.
１２～１３歳の子供たち
７人で編成された部隊だ。
They're young,
but extremely talented.
いずれも幼くして
秀でた才能を持つ者たち。
It was decided
they were ready for war,
彼らなら
戦場に出るには　頃合いと→
and I assigned them to start
with the supply unit.
まずは　補給部隊を任せたが…
早かったか。
I guess it was premature…
So Omoi knew that…
では　オモイは　そのことを知って…。
That idiot!
あのバカ野郎！
Check on the chakra levels
on Battlefield Seven.
第７戦線のチャクラを調べろ！
部隊の生存状況は？
Is anyone in the unit alive?!
White Zetsu are overrunning the area.
白ゼツたちに
埋め尽くされています。
As for chakra from our side…
seven are present.
生存する味方のチャクラは　７つ。
Seven…
The same number as
the Thundercloud Unit.
雷雲隊と同じ…。
Don't even think about it,
Lord Raikage!
何　うちらに都合のいいこと
考えてるんだよ　雷影様！
Those kids knew exactly
what they were getting into.
あの子たちだって
戦場に出たからには→
They were prepared to die
in the battlefield.
命を落とすことだって
覚悟していたはずだろ！
Those kids…are alive.
（オモイ）アイツら　生きてるっすよ。
Damn it! Omoi!
Omoi!
Sorry, everyone.
どうも　すみません　皆さん。
Omoi! Return to your post!
オモイ　持ち場に戻れ！
We're at war! You can't just
do whatever you want!
Please give me one hour.
I'll bring every one of them
back in one hour.
１時間でヤツら全員
無事に連れ戻してきますから》
なっ！？　ふざけたこと
言ってんじゃねえぞ！
Will you stop all this nonsense?!
How can you be so easygoing
and say such a thing?!
何　お気楽なこと言ってんだよ！
What happened to the guy
who's always so worried.
Every unit has lost members.
It's just wishful thinking
to assume that
the seven survivors are all
from the Thundercloud Unit.
Sorry. But the seven are those kids.
Still…
You'll never make it,
even if you depart now.
We're done here if
you're just gonna bore me.
《…んな　眠たいこと言うなら
もう相手しねえよ。　じゃあな》
See ya!
Hey, Omoi!
おい　オモイ！　オモイ！！
Omoi!
Knowing them,
they've already taken down
the enemy and are celebrating.
They could even be into
their second round of partying.
"We can't have any alcohol, okay?
So let's toast with juice."
Man, if they say that,
it's gonna last until morning…
No good, he's not answering.
《雷影様　すみません！
Lord Raikage! I'm so sorry!
あんなバカ　すぐにとっ捕まえて→
Please capture that fool and tie him up,
or whatever!
縛り首にでも
何でもしてください》
But if there are survivors
from the Thundercloud…
だが　もし雷雲隊の者が
生き残っておったら…。
《ヤツらだけ特別扱いには
できないでしょうが！》
We can't give them
any special treatment!
Kakashi, Guy, Lee, Sai…
You can handle things there
for about one hour, can't you?
Huh?
ん？
Even if it's just for an hour,
losing someone strong
like Omoi hurts.
But we'll manage.
If we try five times harder, no,
ten times harder, it's possible.
任せてください。
Just leave it to us!
I'll fight a hundred times harder!
（リー）僕は　１００倍　頑張ります！
マイペースで。
I'll do things my own way…
だそうだ。
Well, you heard them.
I'm grateful.
《すまん…　オモイ…　頼む》
Sorry, Omoi…
I'm counting on you.
But Omoi alone…
しかし　オモイ１人か。
ナルトの影分身たちの位置は？
Give me the position of
Naruto's Shadow Clones!
That kid…?
小僧か？
Just one of his Shadow Clones
has the strength
ヤツなら　影分身１体でも
里１つ分の戦力はある。
to protect an entire village.
（シカク）火影様
それは言いすぎでは…。
Lady Hokage,
that's overstating it a bit.
There's just one…
A Shadow Clone is headed in
the direction of Battlefield Seven…
Although he's not that close.
Notify Naruto!
I promised Lord Raikage
that I'd do it one hour.
But what if I finish this up
in 30 minutes?
What if he's so impressed,
he says,
"Good job!
You're the next Raikage!"
なんてことに…》
Oh but…
Rather than one hour,
it could take three hours.
Then he might say,
"Go back to the village!"
All right, I'm getting close.
Beyond this hill,
the land will be all cleared
with nary a blade of grass…
They'll have rolled out
the red carpet,
and hung up a banner
for me that says,
"Welcome, Omoi!"
またまた…　ドッキリっしょ？　これ…。
Are you kidding me?
Is this a prank?
The Hidden Mist's…
フフフフフフ…。
ハハハハハ…。
You know, you can't stop us…
（ゼツ）いくらでも
相手になってあげるから。
Damn…you guys!
Where the hell's the red carpet?!
Sorry, but this doesn't mean
I'm going to give up!
（ナルト）うずまきナルト　ただいま参上！
Naruto Uzumaki!
At your service!
You're…?!
That Jinchuriki from before…
Naruto Uzumaki!
Rasengan Barrage!
《すげぇ…》
Amazing…
You're Omoi, right?
I don't understand
what's going on…
But I believe you.
Huh?
Those kids are alive!
Save them, no matter what.
This isn't about believing.
They're alive and they're waiting.
Yeah!
They're coming!
《コイツがいれば…。
With him here…
そうよ　あっという間に
コイツら　やっつけて→
We can take care of these guys!
３０分どころか
２０分で片づけて帰れば→
Instead of thirty minutes,
I can finish this in twenty.
やっぱり　お前が雷影だ！
なんてことに…》
And Lord Raikage will say,
"I was right.
You are the next Raikage…"
Come on!
えっ…。
あれ？
Huh?!
Uh-oh… I did it!
ハア…　よかった…　影分身か。
Oh, good. It was a Shadow Clone.
って　全然よくねえ！！
せっかくのナルトが！　バカ　俺！！
It's not good at all!
Naruto was nice enough to…
I'm such a fool!
Naruto probably thought
I could handle it alone and purposely…
let himself get hit!
Yeah… These guys aren't that good.
I can handle them alone!
Those kids are alive!
On second thought,
《やっぱり　３０分は無理かな…
１時間も無理だろうな。
it's impossible to do this
in thirty minutes.
Even with an hour,
it still wouldn't be possible...
How about two hours?
If I get it done in two hours,
maybe Lord Raikage
will give me a break…
次の雷影候補に
してくれるかもしれねえが…》
and still name me as a candidate
to become the next Raikage…
What the…?
The poison gas they're exhaling…
Red dirt?
白いヤツが赤くなった…。
The white guys turned red…
赤い土と関係あんのか？
Does it have something to do
with the red dirt?
What do I do?
どうすっか…。
Beyond this point lies
a field of poison.
こっから向こうは毒の原。
なんだ？　あれ…。
What is that?
いる！
Found them.
They're in there…
I'm sure of it!
They're alive!
《生きてる！》
They're alive… They're alive…
They're alive!
They're definitely alive!
No! Stay away!
Get out of here!
(（ユカイ）ダメだ。　すぐに見つかる))
It's no good.
We'll be found right away.
いずれ　ヤツら　ここに気がつく。
They'll be on to us sooner or later.
空気だって　もう…。
And we're going to run out of air.
無理だったんだ。
まだ　俺たちに戦闘なんて…。
It was too much for us.
We weren't ready for battle.
That's why Lord Raikage assigned us
to the supply unit.
だから　雷影様は
補給部隊にして…。
It's too late for that!
Why didn't you oppose it
when Yukai suggested that
we go and help?
どうして　反対しなかったのよ？
ごめん。　ただ　僕は
何もできなかったことが悔しくて。
Sorry… I'm just frustrated that
we weren't able to do anything!
So am I…
俺も。
私もよ　ユカイ。
I'm mad too, Yukai.
申し訳ないと思っている。
リーダーとしての　俺の判断が…。
I feel horrible that my decision
as a leader…
俺は悔しいんだ。
I can't stand this either.
どうせ　このまま死を待つなら→
If we're just going to wait
for death like this…
最後は　みんなで格好つけよう。
Let's go out with a big bang, together!
《水中に逃げたはいいが→
I jumped in the water to get away…
結果　息できねえのは
一緒じゃねえか》
But I still can't breathe!
《やべえ　もう限界だ…》
Damn it, I've reached my limit…
雷遁　サンダーボルト！
Lightning Style!
Thunderbolt!
This is…
《生きてる…》
They're alive… They're alive…
They're alive!
（みんな）うわ～っ！
Even if we all die,
if we can at least deal a blow…!
Just one blow!
My big brother gave me…this…
《オモイの兄ちゃん…》
Big Brother Omoi!
Lightning Style!
Team Thunder Bomb!
うわ～っ！
《ここの赤土は
水分含みまくりだからな。
This red soil is rich in moisture.
So naturally, the conductivity
of the Lightning Style
is gonna be amazing.
ねぇ　大丈夫だよね？
It's okay to breathe, right?
Yeah, but it's not as fresh
as a mountain breeze…
I've used up my chakra…
Big Bro Omoi, give us a chance
to look good too.
Well, I guess you guys can manage.
Let's go!
Didn't I tell you they were alive?
持ち場を離れ
勝手な行動したヤツが→
Someone who left his post and
acted without orders
has no right to talk!
弟たちにも言っとけ。
And tell your inexperienced subordinates
not to show off!
半人前のくせして
格好つけんじゃねえって。
Nope, it's about time
they started showing off.
格好つけたってよ。
These guys have come of age.
Omoi! You greenhorn!
雷影様！
L-Lord Raikage!
約束は１時間以内だ。
それまでに帰ってこないと→
I gave you one hour, no more!
If you don't return within that time,
I will punish you myself!
わし自ら仕置きするから覚悟しろ。
わかりました！
So be prepared!
I understand!
《サンキューな　オモイ》
Thanks… Omoi.
I bet I'm gonna fall into
a hole somewhere…
and I'll be stuck because
it's so deep…
and I won't be able to get out and
the clock will keep ticking…
約束の時間が過ぎちゃって…。
and I won't make it back
by the promised time…
で　雷影様の雷が…》
and I'll incur Lord Raikage's wrath and…
Oh man, why am I always
so unlucky?
I finally caught up!
You're late! What were you doing?
A persistent pee, yo.